tigraionline.com 2016-05-11

# Tigrai Online.com Privacy Policy

Tigrai Online  
March. 24 2011

Tigrai Online - tigraionline.com respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our web sites. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to [www.tigraionline.com](http://www.tigraionline.com/) will be known only to two parties: you and [www.tigraionline.com.](http://www.tigraionline.com/) The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site. Personal information includes your name, e-mail addresses, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.

**Use of tigraionline.com cookies**  
As a matter of policy we at Tigrai Online don’t use cookies to collect information from our visitors. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. If you provide your e-mail address for any reason, we will not share it with anyone and no one.

**Disclosure of personal information**  
tigraionline.com will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any public forum within our Web site.

**Other sites**  
tigraionline.com contains many links to other sites on the world wide Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

Third Party Advertising... We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

Third Party Cookies... In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

## More Articles

Sponsored Links
